# **ANDREA BRUNI**

Junior Web Developer

📞 +49 1577 8618144 @ andrea.brn8@gmail.com 🕜 linkedin.com/in/andrea-bruni-06240213b 🗣 Hamburg, Germany

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Bartender

UWE Reeperbahn GmbH 09/2023 - 01/2024 Hamburg, Germany Fancy cocktail bar located in the heart of Hamburg's nightlife.

- · Mixology expertise knowledge for creating classic and modern cocktails.
- Elevated customer experience, leading to a 30% increase in tips collected by implementing creative cocktail presentations.

#### Front Desk Receptionist

Fourservice GECS 09/2022 - 07/2023 Hamburg, Germany

Provides trained and professional receptionists to hotels, ensuring exceptional guest service and excellent front desk operations.

- · Managed over 250 guest check-ins and check-outs each day maintaining a 98% accuracy rate in booking management.
- · Efficient in handling multiple tasks simultaneously.

#### Tester

Quick Coronatest 01/2022 - 05/2022 Hamburg, Germany

- · Conduct oral and nasal swab tests.
- · Documentation recording procedures in the system.
- Enhanced test efficiency by 30%, reducing testing cycle times and accelerating product delivery.

#### Operations and Office Management

Breeze Technologies 10/2021 - 01/2022 Hamburg, Germany

 Achieved 100% on-time project delivery by streamlining communication and workflow processes.

### Bartender

M&V Gaststätte 10/2018 - 06/2021 Hamburg, Germany

- · Managed bar operations during high-volume events with over 300 attendees, ensuring quality service.
- Handled nightly cash transactions averaging €3,000 on weekends, demonstrating trust and reliability.

#### Waiter

InterCity Hotel 02/2018 - 10/2018 Hamburg, Germany

#### Bartender

Fattoria Toccaferro 03/2017 - 11/2017 Pescara, Italy

### Waiter

Restaurante Casa Montesdeoca 10/2015 - 08/2016 Las Palmas de Gran Canaria, Spain

- · Managed service for up to 150 guests per shift, ensuring a smooth dining experience for patrons.
- Achieved a 98% positive customer feedback score by enhancing dining experience, leading to a 20% increase in repeat business.
- · I translated the menus and information for Casa Montesdeoca restaurant into Italian, English, and German, enhancing the experience for international customers.

#### Cashier

Zattis GmbH 04/2013 - 09/2015 Ingolstadt, Germany

## Bartender

Stella D'Oro Restaurant 03/2012 - 04/2013 Ingolstadt, Germany

#### SUMMARY

After several years working in the gastronomy and hotel industry across Europe I decided to complete my high school diploma.

Pushed by a strong passion for technology and programming, I completed a course in web development with the aim of starting a new professional career.

#### **EDUCATION**

Professional Certificate in Law - Biology Campus Zweiter Bildungsweg, Hamburg 02/2022 - 01/2024 Hamburg, Germany

Qualification, Visual Arts (Photography, Movie and Graphics)

Institute of Art V. Bellisario 09/2008 - 06/2011 Pescara, Italy

Web Development Bootcamp SPICED Academy 04/2024 - 07/2024 Remote

#### LANGUAGES

Italian	Native	••••
German	C2	••••
English	C1	••••
Spanish	C1	••••

# SKILLS

Operating Systems

Windows • Mac

Tools

HTML5 • CSS • Javascript • Next.js • React •

MongoDB • GitHub • ORACLE

Microsoft Office

Word • Excel • PowerPoint • Outlook

#### CERTIFICATION

Web Development **SPICED** Academy